Guide to the Sarah G. Jacobson Papers MSS.157
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIII: 2018 Accretion, 1953-2012; 14 VHS; 17 DVDs; 30 MiniDV; 7 CDs; 4 DAT; 1 audiocassette; 1 Half_Inch_Video_Reel; 4.22 Gigabytes in 6057 computer files
  The majority of this series has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor. In March 2025, the born digital materials were arranged alphabetically at the end of the inventory.
  This accretion includes production materials from Sarah G. Jacobson's independent film projects and freelance writing. The bulk of the material relates to Jacobson's professional career, primarily the production of her films Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore and I Was A Teenage Serial Killer. These materials consist of notebooks, photographs, correspondence, 68 video recordings, and 8 born-digital CD-R's from her directing projects, as well as collections of Jacobson's published writing. Full-length digital recordings of Jacobson's shorts include I Was A Teenage Serial Killer, The Fabulous Stains: Behind the Movie, High School Reunion, Road Movie, Sweet Miss, Bra Shopping, Man or Astroman, and a music video for the British punk band Fluffy. Photography from the production of Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore, multiple Sundance Film Festivals, and a launch party for the Fluffy music video. Jacobson's freelance writing on modern film from 1995 to 1998 published in fanzines, underground film and music publications such as Filth and Film Threat, as well as commercial publications Sassy and YM represent her contributions to film journalism. In addition, this accretion includes classwork and notebooks from 1987 to 2004, personal correspondence, and journals.
  - Notebook, 1985-2012 (Box 35, Folder 1-6, 9-22, Box 37, Folder 1-21, 29, Box 38, Folder 2-3, Box 36, Folder 1-6, 8-20)
  - Photographs, 1995-1998 (Box 38, Folder 4-7, 10-12, Box 37, Folder 26-28)
  - Merla in Oz, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Sympathy letters, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Ohio, Pennsylvania, 1953-2012 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - SLAA, Undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - ACLU, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - My Hipster Indie Film Column, 1995-1997 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Glasses, Undated (Box 40)
  - Bachelors degree, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Posters, Undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence -- Electronic Records, 1994-2012
    - Personal, FA_MSS_157_ER_2
    - Professional, FA_MSS_157_ER_3
  - Sarah Jacobson's Shorts, circa 1993-1999; FA_MSS_157_ER_1
  - Writing and Research -- Electronic Records
    - Journals, 1994-2002; FA_MSS_157_ER_4
    - Professional Writing, 1996-2002; FA_MSS_157_ER_5
    - Research Material and Writing by Others, 2001-2002; FA_MSS_157_ER_6